<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tanzu Validated Solutions</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/</link><description>Recent content on Tanzu Validated Solutions</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tkg-nsxt-airgap.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tkg-nsxt-airgap.html</guid><description>﻿# Deploy Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on vSphere with NSX-T Networking in Air-gapped Environment
VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid (TKG) (multi-cloud) provides organizations with a consistent, upstream-compatible, regional Kubernetes substrate that is ready for end-user workloads and ecosystem integrations. It delivers an open source aligned Kubernetes distribution with consistent operations and management to support infrastructure and app modernization.
An air-gapped installation method is used when the Tanzu Kubernetes Grid components (bootstrapper and cluster nodes) are unable to connect to the Internet to download the installation binaries from the public VMware Registry during Tanzu Kubernetes Grid installation or upgrade.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tkg-vsphere-vds-airgap.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tkg-vsphere-vds-airgap.html</guid><description>﻿# Deploy Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on vSphere Networking in an Air-Gapped Environment
VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid (TKG) provides a consistent, upstream-compatible, regional Kubernetes substrate that is ready for end-user workloads and ecosystem integrations.
An air-gap installation method is used when the Tanzu Kubernetes Grid bootstrapper and cluster nodes components are unable to connect to the Internet to download the installation binaries from the public VMware Registry during Tanzu Kubernetes Grid installation or upgrades.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-pinniped-with-tkg.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-pinniped-with-tkg.html</guid><description>﻿# Authentication with Pinniped
Tanzu Kubernetes Grid implements user authentication with Pinniped, an open-source authentication service for Kubernetes clusters. Pinniped allows you to plug external OpenID Connect (OIDC) or LDAP identity providers (IdP) into Tanzu Kubernetes (workload) clusters so that you can control user access to those clusters.
For LDAP authentication, Pinniped uses Dex as the endpoint to connect to your upstream LDAP IdP. If you use OIDC, Pinniped provides its own endpoint, so Dex is not required.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tkg-nsxt-airgap-ra.md.old.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tkg-nsxt-airgap-ra.md.old.html</guid><description>﻿# Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on NSX-T Networking in Airgap Environment - Reference Design
VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid (multi-cloud) provides organizations with a consistent, upstream-compatible, regional Kubernetes substrate that is ready for end-user workloads and ecosystem integrations.
An air-gapped environment is a network security measure employed to ensure a computer or computer network is secure by physically isolating it from unsecured networks, such as the public Internet or an unsecured local area network.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tkg-nsxt-airgap-ra.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tkg-nsxt-airgap-ra.html</guid><description>﻿# Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on vSphere with NSX-T Networking in Air-Gapped Environment Reference Design
VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid (multi-cloud) provides organizations with a consistent, upstream-compatible, regional Kubernetes substrate that is ready for end-user workloads and ecosystem integrations.
An air-gapped environment is a network security measure employed to ensure a computer or computer network is secure by physically isolating it from unsecured networks, such as the public Internet or an unsecured local area network.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/snippets/supported-component-matrix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/snippets/supported-component-matrix/</guid><description>The validated Bill of Materials that can be used to install Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on your vSphere with NSX-T environment is as follows:
Software Components Version Tanzu Kubernetes Grid 1.5.1 VMware vSphere ESXi 7.0 U2 and later VMware vCenter (VCSA) 7.0 U2 and later VMware vSAN 7.0 U2 and later NSX Advanced Load Balancer 20.1.7 For up-to-date information about which software versions can be used together, check the Interoperability Matrix here.</description></item><item><title>Architecture Overview</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tap-architecture-planning.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tap-architecture-planning.html</guid><description>Architecture Overview This architecture gives you a path to creating a production deployment of Tanzu Application Platform 1.2. However, do not feel constrained to follow this exact path if your specific use cases warrant a different architecture.
Design decisions enumerated in this document exemplify the main design issues you will encounter in planning your Tanzu Application Platform environment and the rationale behind a chosen solution path. Understanding these decisions can help provide a rationale for any necessary deviation from this architecture.</description></item><item><title>Architecture Overview</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tkg-edge.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tkg-edge.html</guid><description>Architecture Overview This solution architecture is intended for anyone responsible for designing, implementing, managing, and securing edge sites, including DevOps administrators, VI administrators, platform operators, and security teams.
Topology Multiple topologies are possible for edge deployments. Some of the topologies are described in this section. However, the VMware Tanzu Edge Solution Architecture uses a centralized or hub and spoke topology, where a vCenter is deployed at the main data center location and a vSphere cluster is deployed in the data center at each edge site.</description></item><item><title>Configure Tanzu SaaS Components for Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-saas-services.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-saas-services.html</guid><description>Configure Tanzu SaaS Components for Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations VMware SaaS services for Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations provide additional Kubernetes lifecycle management, observability, and service mesh features. This document outlines the configuration needed to set up the following VMware SaaS services.
Tanzu Mission Control (TMC) Tanzu Observability (TO) Tanzu Service Mesh (TSM) Tanzu Mission Control Tanzu Mission Control (TMC) is a centralized management platform for operating and securing your Kubernetes infrastructure and modern applications across multiple teams and clouds.</description></item><item><title>Customize Tanzu Observability Dashboard for Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-to-customized-dashboard.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-to-customized-dashboard.html</guid><description>﻿
Customize Tanzu Observability Dashboard for Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations Tanzu Observability provides various out-of-the-box dashboards. You can customize the dashboards for your particular deployment. This document provides the steps to customize the dashboards to monitor the following Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations components:
Tanzu Kubernetes Grid Clusters VMware vSphere NSX Advanced Load Balancer We will customize the following dashboards:
Summary Dashboard Resource Utilization Dashboard Health Check Dashboard Network Dashboard Prerequisites Ensure that Tanzu Observability is fetching data from the following: Tanzu Kubernetes Grid Clusters, NSX Advanced Load Balancer, and VMware vSphere.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-overview.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-overview.html</guid><description>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations The following provide deployment instructions for the Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations reference designs. The deployments use example configuration values. Therefore, make sure to use configuration values that are appropriate for your environment.
Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on AWS: Outlines the steps for deploying VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes operations on AWS. The deployment is based on the reference design provided in VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on AWS Reference Design.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on AWS</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-aws.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-aws.html</guid><description>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on AWS This document outlines the steps for deploying VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on AWS. The deployment is based on the reference design provided in VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on AWS Reference Design.
Deploying with VMware Service Installer for Tanzu You can use VMware Service Installer for VMware Tanzu to automate this deployment.
VMware Service Installer for Tanzu automates the deployment of the reference designs for Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on Microsoft Azure</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-azure.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-azure.html</guid><description>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on Microsoft Azure VMware Tanzu simplifies the operations of Kubernetes for multi-cloud deployments by centralizing management and governance for clusters and teams across on-premises, public clouds, and the edge. It delivers an open source aligned Kubernetes distribution with consistent operations and management to support infrastructure and app modernization.
This document provides a step-by-step guide for how to install and deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes operations on Microsoft Azure.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on VMware Cloud on AWS</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-in-vmc-aws.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-in-vmc-aws.html</guid><description>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on VMware Cloud on AWS This document provides step-by-step instructions for deploying Tanzu Kubernetes Operations on VMware Cloud on AWS.
The scope of the document is limited to providing the deployment steps based on the reference design in VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on VMware Cloud on AWS Reference Design.
Deploying with VMware Service Installer for Tanzu You can use VMware Service Installer for VMware Tanzu to automate this deployment.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-vsphere.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-vsphere.html</guid><description>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere This document provides step-by-step instructions for deploying and configuring Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on a vSphere environment backed by a Virtual Distributed Switch (VDS). The scope of the document is limited to providing the deployment steps based on the reference design in VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere Reference Design. This document does not cover any deployment procedures for the underlying SDDC components.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere with VMware VDS</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-vsphere-vds.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-vsphere-vds.html</guid><description>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere with VMware VDS This document provides step-by-step instructions for installing and configuring Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on a vSphere environment backed by a Virtual Distributed Switch (VDS). The deployment is based on the reference design provided in VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere Reference Design. This document does not provide instructions for deploying the underlying SDDC components.
Deploying with VMware Service Installer for Tanzu You can use VMware Service Installer for VMware Tanzu to automate this deployment.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations using vSphere with Tanzu</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-vsphere-with-tanzu.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-vsphere-with-tanzu.html</guid><description>Deploy Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations using vSphere with Tanzu This document outlines the steps for deploying Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations using vSphere with Tanzu in a vSphere environment backed by a Virtual Distributed Switch (VDS) and leveraging NSX Advanced Load Balancer (ALB) for L4/L7 load balancing and ingress.
The scope of the document is limited to providing deployment steps based on the reference design in VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations using vSphere with Tanzu Reference Design.</description></item><item><title>Deploy Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on AWS in an Air-Gapped Environment</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-aws-airgap.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-aws-airgap.html</guid><description>Deploy Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on AWS in an Air-Gapped Environment This document outlines the steps for deploying VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on AWS in an air-gapped (Internet-restricted) environment. The deployment is based on the reference design provided in VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on AWS Airgap Reference Design.
Deploying with VMware Service Installer for Tanzu You can use VMware Service Installer for VMware Tanzu to automate this deployment.
VMware Service Installer for Tanzu automates the deployment of the reference designs for Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations.</description></item><item><title>Deploy User-Managed Packages in Workload Clusters</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tkg-package-install.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tkg-package-install.html</guid><description>Deploy User-Managed Packages in Workload Clusters After creating workload clusters, you can install user-managed packages. These packages extend the core functionality of the Kubernetes clusters created by Tanzu Kubernetes Grid.
For example, you can install the Contour package to implement ingress control, the Harbor package to configure a private container registry, or the Fluent Bit, Grafana, and Prometheus packages to collect logs and metrics from your clusters.
You can install Tanzu packages via the CLI by invoking the tanzu package install command or directly from Tanzu Mission Control by utilizing the TMC Catalog feature.</description></item><item><title>Deploy VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on VMware vSphere with VMware NSX-T</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-vsphere-nsxt.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tko-on-vsphere-nsxt.html</guid><description>Deploy VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on VMware vSphere with VMware NSX-T This document provides step-by-step instructions for deploying Tanzu Kubernetes Operations in a vSphere environment backed by NSX-T Data Center networking.
The scope of the document is limited to providing deployment steps based on the reference design in VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere with NSX-T. It does not cover deployment procedures for the underlying SDDC components.
Deploying with VMware Service Installer for Tanzu You can use VMware Service Installer for VMware Tanzu to automate this deployment.</description></item><item><title>Enable Data Protection on a Workload Cluster and Configure Backup</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tkg-data-protection.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tkg-data-protection.html</guid><description>Enable Data Protection on a Workload Cluster and Configure Backup You can run backup and restore operations in Tanzu Mission Control to protect your Kubernetes data.
Prerequisites Before you enable Data Protection on a workload cluster, ensure the following prerequisites:
You have an active Tanzu Mission Control subscription.
The workload cluster that you want to protect is registered or attached with Tanzu Mission Control.
You have created a credential for Data Protection as per instructions provided in the Tanzu Mission Control documentation.</description></item><item><title>Prepare External Identity Management</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-pinniped-with-tkg.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-pinniped-with-tkg.html</guid><description>Prepare External Identity Management Tanzu Kubernetes Grid implements user authentication with Pinniped. Pinniped allows you to plug external OpenID Connect (OIDC) or LDAP identity providers (IDP) into Tanzu Kubernetes clusters, so that you can control user access to those clusters.
You can enable identity management during or after management cluster deployment. Any workload clusters that you create after enabling identity management are automatically configured to use the same identity provider as the management cluster.</description></item><item><title>Tanzu Application Platform 1.2 Planning and Architecture Reference</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-index-tap.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-index-tap.html</guid><description>Tanzu Application Platform 1.2 Planning and Architecture Reference Tanzu Application Platform Planning and Architecture Reference provides a standard architecture for deploying Tanzu Application Platform (TAP) 1.2. The document covers topics such as Kubernetes requirements and cluster layout for Tanzu Application Platform. For guidance on how to deploy your particular Kubernetes distribution, see the reference architecture for that distribution.</description></item><item><title>Tanzu Application Platform Deployment</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tap.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/deployment-guides-tap.html</guid><description>Tanzu Application Platform Deployment This deployment outlines the deployment steps for VMware Tanzu Application Platform 1.1 on a Kubernetes workload cluster. In accordance with the Tanzu Application Platform Reference Design, four clusters will be created:
Tanzu Application Platform Build Cluster Tanzu Application Platform Run Cluster Tanzu Application Platform View Cluster Tanzu Application Platform Iterate Cluster Prerequisites Before deploying VMware Tanzu Application Platform, ensure that the following prerequisites are met:
A Tanzu Network account is available for downloading Tanzu Application Platform packages.</description></item><item><title>Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations SaaS Integration</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-saas.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-saas.html</guid><description>Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations SaaS Integration The SaaS products in the VMware Tanzu portfolio are critical components for securing your IT infrastructure. VMware Tanzu Mission Control provides a centralized control plane for Kubernetes, and Tanzu Service Mesh provides a global control plane for service mesh networks. VMware Tanzu Observability by Wavefront offers observability and analytics for multi-cloud Kubernetes environments.
The following VMware SaaS services provide additional Kubernetes lifecycle management, observability, and service mesh features.</description></item><item><title>Tanzu Kubernetes Grid Data Protection</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-data-protection.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-data-protection.html</guid><description>Tanzu Kubernetes Grid Data Protection Kubernetes maintains many states stored in the cluster itself in addition to your application state. Config maps, custom resource definitions, and secrets are all stored in the Kubernetes control plane. All of these are critical to your clusters’ operations. Protecting this data is just as critical as protecting any other element of your IT infrastructure, so it should be covered by data protection and your disaster recovery plan.</description></item><item><title>Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on vSphere Networking in an Air-Gapped Environment Reference Design</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tkg-vsphere-vds-airgap.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tkg-vsphere-vds-airgap.html</guid><description>Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on vSphere Networking in an Air-Gapped Environment Reference Design VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid (multi-cloud) provides organizations with a consistent, upstream-compatible, regional Kubernetes substrate that is ready for end-user workloads and ecosystem integrations.
An air-gapped environment is a network security measure employed to ensure a computer or computer network is secure by physically isolating it from unsecured networks, such as the public Internet or an unsecured local area network.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu Edge Solution Reference Architecture 1.0</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-index-edge.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-index-edge.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu Edge Solution Reference Architecture 1.0 Edge computing is gaining a lot of momentum for a variety of reasons that range from avoidance of latency, data volume, and bandwidth considerations to the need for autonomous disconnected operations, privacy, and security. These reasons are pushing businesses across all industries to run more and more applications at edge sites. Traditionally, these applications are run on VMs, but with the emergence of Kubernetes and microservices architectures, more applications are being containerized and there is a need for running a cloud native compute stack at the edge.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on AWS Reference Design</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-aws.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-aws.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on AWS Reference Design VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations simplifies operation of Kubernetes for multi-cloud deployment by centralizing management and governance for clusters and teams across on-premises, public clouds, and edge. Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations delivers an open source aligned Kubernetes distribution with consistent operations and management to support infrastructure and application modernization.
This document lays out a reference design for deploying VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations with Tanzu components on AWS.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on Azure Reference Design</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-azure.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-azure.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on Azure Reference Design VMware Tanzu simplifies the operation of Kubernetes in multi-cloud environment by centralizing management and governance for clusters and teams across on-premises, public clouds, and the edge. It delivers an open-source-aligned Kubernetes distribution with consistent operations and management to support infrastructure and app modernization.
This document lays out a reference design for deploying VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations with Tanzu components on Microsoft Azure.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on VMware Cloud on AWS Reference Design</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vmc-aws.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vmc-aws.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on VMware Cloud on AWS Reference Design Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations simplifies operating Kubernetes for multi-cloud deployment by centralizing management and governance for clusters and teams across on-premises, public clouds, and edge. Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations delivers an open source aligned Kubernetes distribution with consistent operations and management to support infrastructure and application modernization.
This document lays out a reference design for deploying VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on VMware Cloud on AWS.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere Reference Design</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vsphere.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vsphere.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere Reference Design Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations simplifies operating Kubernetes for multi-cloud deployment by centralizing management and governance for clusters and teams across on-premises, public clouds, and edge. It delivers an open source aligned Kubernetes distribution with consistent operations and management to support infrastructure and app modernization.
This document describes a reference design for deploying VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere backed by vSphere Networking (VDS).</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere with NSX-T Reference Design</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vsphere-nsx.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vsphere-nsx.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere with NSX-T Reference Design VMware Tanzu simplifies operation of Kubernetes for multi-cloud deployment by centralizing management and governance for clusters and teams across on-premises, public clouds, and edge. It delivers an open source aligned Kubernetes distribution with consistent operations and management to support infrastructure and application modernization.
This document lays out a reference architecture related for VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations when deployed on a vSphere environment backed by NSX-T and offers a high-level overview of the different components.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations Reference Architecture 1.5</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-index.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations Reference Architecture 1.5 Kubernetes is great platform that provides development teams with a single API to deploy, manage, and run applications. However, running, maintaining, and securing Kubernetes is a complex task. VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations simplifies Kubernetes operations. It determines what base OS instances to use, which Kubernetes Container Network Interface (CNI) and Container Storage Interfaces (CSI) to use, how to secure the Kubernetes API, and much more.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations using vSphere with Tanzu on NSX-T Reference Design</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vsphere-with-tanzu-nsxt.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vsphere-with-tanzu-nsxt.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations using vSphere with Tanzu on NSX-T Reference Design vSphere with Tanzu transforms vSphere into a platform for running Kubernetes workloads natively on the hypervisor layer. When vSphere with Tanzu is enabled on a vSphere cluster, you can run Kubernetes workloads directly on ESXi hosts and create upstream Kubernetes clusters within dedicated resource pools.
This document lays out a reference design for deploying VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations on vSphere with Tanzu enabled.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations using vSphere with Tanzu Reference Design</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vsphere-with-tanzu.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-vsphere-with-tanzu.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations using vSphere with Tanzu Reference Design vSphere with Tanzu transforms the vSphere cluster into a platform for running Kubernetes workloads in dedicated resource pools. When vSphere with Tanzu is enabled on a vSphere cluster, vSphere with Tanzu creates a Kubernetes control plane directly in the hypervisor layer. You can then run Kubernetes containers by creating upstream Kubernetes clusters through the VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid Service and run your applications inside these clusters.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid 1.5 Air-Gapped Reference Design and Deployment</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-index-air-gap.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-index-air-gap.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid 1.5 Air-Gapped Reference Design and Deployment You can deploy Tanzu Kubernetes Grid management clusters and Tanzu Kubernetes Grid workload clusters in air-gapped environments that do not have a physical connection to the Internet.
This documentation provides reference designs for deploying Tanzu Kubernetes Grid in an air-gapped environment. The documentation also includes the steps to deploy Tanzu Kubernetes Grid in an air-gapped environment on AWS.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on AWS Air-Gapped Reference Design</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-aws-airgap.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-aws-airgap.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on AWS Air-Gapped Reference Design VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid (multi-cloud) provides a consistent, upstream-compatible, regional Kubernetes substrate that is ready for end-user workloads and ecosystem integrations.
This document lays out a reference design for deploying VMware Tanzu for Kubernetes Grid on AWS Networking in an air-gapped environment with Tanzu components on AWS. An air-gapped environment is a network security measure employed to ensure that a computer or computer network is secure by physically isolating it from unsecured networks, such as the public Internet or an unsecured local area network.</description></item><item><title>VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on Hybrid-Cloud Azure</title><link>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-azure-hybrid.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://craigtracey.github.io/validated-solutions/reference-designs-tko-on-azure-hybrid.html</guid><description>VMware Tanzu Kubernetes Grid on Hybrid-Cloud Azure A validated augmentation for the TKO on Azure reference architecture
Summary Building on the reference architecture provided for Tanzu for Kubernetes Operations (TKO) on Azure, this document outlines the modifications that should be considered for a hybrid-cloud architecture. This type of cloud architecture maintains some dependency or connectivity to on-prem networks and systems, and special considerations must be made to co-exist within this scenario.</description></item></channel></rss>